<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tashkent travel</string>
    <string name="object_name">object name</string>
    <string name="address">address</string>
    <string name="information">information</string>
    <string name="location"><u>Location</u></string>
    <string name="phone"><u>Phone</u></string>
    <string name="work_time">work_time</string>

    <string name="name_mosque_khazrati_imam">Mosque Khazrati Imam</string>
    <string name="name_mosque_sheikh_zayniddin">Mosque Sheikh Zayniddin</string>
    <string name="name_mosque_minor">Mosque Minor</string>
    <string name="name_mosque_islam_ota">Mosque Islam Ota</string>
    <string name="name_mosque_shekh_muhammadsodik">Mosque Sheikh Muhammad Sadyk Muhammad Yusuf</string>
    <string name="name_hotel_hyatt_regency">Hyatt Regency Hotel</string>
    <string name="name_hotel_hilton">Hilton Tashkent City Hotel</string>
    <string name="name_hotel_ichan_qala">Ichan Qal\'a Premium Class Hotel</string>
    <string name="name_hotel_wyndham">Wyndham Tashkent Hotel</string>
    <string name="name_hotel_city_palace">City Palace Hotel Tashkent</string>
    <string name="name_shopping_samarkand_darvoza">Mall Samarkand Darvoza</string>
    <string name="name_shopping_chorsu_bazaar">Chorsu Bazaar</string>
    <string name="name_shopping_yangiabad">Yangiobod Weekend Flea Market</string>
    <string name="name_shopping_next">Next Mall</string>
    <string name="name_shopping_megaplanet">Mega Planet</string>
    <string name="name_museums_nature">State Museum of Nature of Uzbekistan</string>
    <string name="name_museums_zoo">Tashkent Zoo</string>
    <string name="name_museums_victory">Victory Park</string>
    <string name="name_museums_temurids">Amir Timur Museum</string>
    <string name="name_museums_railways">Railway Museum</string>

    <string name="info_mosque_khazrati_imam">Thoroughly restored in 2007, the historic buildings of
        the complex, with the earliest of them dating back to the 16th century, show their original
        splendor now. The new mosque featuring traditional Islamic architectural elements adds to
        the grandeur of the site.</string>
    <string name="info_mosque_sheikh_zayniddin">\"Sheyh Zayniddin\" Jami mosque and mausoleum widely
        known in Tashkent as \"Kukcha\" mosque is located in Mannon Uygur street 378, in a small Tashkent
        district known among locals as Kukcha. \"Sheyh Zayniddin\" mosque and the cemetery next to it
        have 700 years history. \nAccording to history professor Omonulla Fayzullaev, Sheyh Zayniddin\'s
        full name is nothing less than \"Sheyh Zayniddin Koyi Orifoni Toshkandi ibn Sheyh Shahobiddin
        Abu Hafs Umar Suhravardi\". He was born in 1164 and died in 1259 when he was 95 years old
        (The exact date of his birth is unknown).</string>
    <string name="info_mosque_minor">Minor mosque - a new architectural complex in Tashkent - the
        capital of Uzbekistan, located on the banks of the canal Anhor, embankment of which in recent
        months has undergone significant changes in terms of improvement.\nThe mosque is designed for
        more than 2,400 people. After opening it has become one of the largest spiritual centers of
        Muslims of Tashkent and Uzbekistan. Its construction was financed by the state budget and the
        Spiritual Administration of Muslims in Uzbekistan.\nThe mosque has all the facilities and
        amenities for the parishioners. There are special rooms for washing, which are equipped with
        all necessary facilities.</string>
    <string name="info_mosque_islam_ota">Islom Ota Mosque is one of the most beautiful mosques in
        Tashkent. It was founded in 2016, but the mosque itself has been around for many years.
        Previously, it was called \"Jurabek\" and in 2015 the mosque suffered from a fire, after which
        reconstruction work was carried out. The Islom Ota Mosque, named after the first President
        of Uzbekistan Islam Karimov, appeared on the site of the old mosque, and the territory of
        the complex has doubled and today can accommodate up to 10 thousand people. There is also
        a library that contains rare editions and original manuscripts. The mosque was built in the
        best traditions of eastern mosques: the complex is decorated with a huge blue dome, a high
        minaret and four small minarets at its corners.</string>
    <string name="info_mosque_shekh_muhammadsodik">The mosque is located next to the \"Sugalli Ota\"
        pilgrimage site. Sheikh Muhammad Sadyk Muhammad Yusuf began its construction.\nOn the territory
        of more than 2 hectares, a complex has been built, which includes a conference hall, classrooms,
        a bathing room, a museum and other auxiliary premises. \nThe \"Sugalli Ota\" mausoleum has
        been restored, and the building of the mosque has been enlarged thanks to the attached iwan.</string>
    <string name="info_hotel_hyatt_regency">Hyatt Regency Tashkent offers bright, spacious guestrooms
        with floor-to-ceiling windows that are elegantly decorated with contemporary furniture and
        locally inspired artwork. Each guestroom has a generous workspace with ergonomic chair and
        charging station, and bathrooms feature a soothing walk-in rain shower with separate bathtub.
        Regency Club rooms and suites include access to the Regency Club Lounge on the sixth floor,
        serving complimentary evening cocktails and hors d\'oeuvres</string>
    <string name="info_hotel_hilton">Get the celebrity treatment with world-class service at Hilton
        Tashkent City\nLocated in Tashkent, Hilton Tashkent City has a bar and a terrace. Among the
        facilities of this property are a restaurant, indoor pool and a Pan-Asian rooftop restaurant
        with city views. The property offers a 24-hour front desk and room service, along with free WiFi
        throughout.\nAll rooms are equipped with air conditioning, minibar, free WiFi and flat-screen TV.
        A private bathroom comes with a separate walk-in rain shower and bath, hairdryer and slippers.
        Free toiletries are featured.</string>
    <string name="info_hotel_ichan_qala">The hotel\'s interior is decorated in Khiva style, in warm
        colors typical of the oriental style, using luxurious fabrics. Each room includes a flat-screen TV,
        refrigerator and a private bathroom with toiletries and hairdryer.The restaurant of the "Ichan Qala"
        hotel offers dishes of local Uzbek cuisine.\nIn addition, guests can visit the lounge bar and
        outdoor terrace, as well as a sauna, jacuzzi and billiards.</string>
    <string name="info_hotel_wyndham">Spacious and modern rooms and suits of the Wyndham Tashkent
        Hotel are perfect for both business and leisure. Such modern facilities as flat-panel high
        definition TVs and free high-speed Internet are available for you. The Hotel is located in
        the city center and is easy to approach by urban transport, and you can reach any place of
        the city, including such popular attractions like the Alay Bazaar, Museum of Timurids’
        History, Chor-su Bazaar and Khast Imam Square at whim.\nThere are two restaurants with
        delicious cuisine and banquet rooms for events such as weddings, corporate meetings,
        etc in the Hotel. A fitness center with indoor and outdoor pools and saunas are at guests
        disposal. Discover the beauty of Tashkent with us.</string>
    <string name="info_hotel_city_palace">City Palace Hotel Tashkent is 1640 feet from Emir Temur
        Square and Emir Timur Museum in the heart of Tashkent city center. Features include an outdoor
        pool, indoor pool, and free WiFi. A mini-bar, seating area, and refrigerator are provided in
        each room as well as a satellite TV. City Palace Hotel Tashkent extras include an electric kettle,
        towels, and linen. A restaurant is on site, and luggage storage is offered at reception for added
        convenience. Free parking is provided. Abdulla Kodiriy metro station is 1148 feet away.\nThe
        hotel is also 2 minutes from Pakhtakor Stadium, 6 minutes drive from Tashkent Botanical Garden,
        and 4.3 minutes from Tashkent International Airport.</string>
    <string name="info_shopping_samarkand_darvoza">Samarkand Darvoza is one of the upscale malls in
        Tashkent which caters to the shopping needs of the customers. This mall is a like a one-stop
        destination for all the necessary items one would want to buy during their visit to this place.
        This shopping mall is a great place to hang out with your gang of buddies in your free time.
        If you are crazy about buying some branded goods, then this mall offers you a good collection
        of items. You can shop from a wide collection of watches and branded clothes along with
        footwear and much more at this place. If you are tired of hopping from stall to the other in
        the mall, then you can visit the food, shopping court and savor some food to
        regain the lost energy. The mall also has a children\’s play area ideally designed with a variety
        of games to keep kids engaged.</string>
    <string name="info_shopping_chorsu_bazaar">Bazaar is the heart of every oriental city, the center
        of public life, breadwinner of the whole city. Since the dawn of time bazaars appeared on the
        intersections of trade roads, on big squares of cities. They played role of main places of the
        city, where merchants, traders and common people gathered to discuss important news, to know
        prices, to have a rest in cozy choykhana (Uzbek café) eating pilaf and drinking green tea.
        Also bazaars were the places of main entertaining events of the city – theatrical performances.
        \nTashkent Bazaar Chorsu, the age of which is more than hundred years, also was always located
        on the main square of the city Eski-Juva. Old bazaar constructions destroyed and went bad,
        but the traditional architecture remained unchanged – domed large premises. This was the only
        way to protect oneself from heat and dust in terms of hot and dry Asian climate.\nThe tendency
        of construction of such bazaars with a complex of covered premises began in XI century and
        went on up to XIII century. In our century this bazaar inherited land and premises of previous
        centuries. The modern trade complex is built with a glance of architectural features and traditions
        of urban development of previous epochs.</string>
    <string name="info_shopping_yangiabad">The flea market \"Yangiobod\" has been famous for its uniqueness
        and coloring for many years. Like all flea markets, the Yangiobod market literally \"boils\" on
        weekends and you can find absolutely everything here. Do you like computers or do you like to
        collect antique things? Or maybe you are looking for fishing equipment for fishing for a weekend
        or you dream about buying a cute little animal? Then you definitely should visit this storehouse
        of all kinds of goods.\nFlea market \"Yangiobod\" is a real collection of a wide variety of
        items and things absolutely for all tastes. Being in Tashkent, you must visit this market,
        where you can find anything you like, and at the same time walk in endless rows and penetrate
        the real life of the city.</string>
    <string name="info_shopping_next">SEC \"NEXT\" is a modern, progressive, family shopping mall,
        opened in 2013 in the Yakkasaray district of Tashkent. The shopping center covers an area of
        25,000 square meters, which includes the building of a shopping mall, a park area, a terrace,
        parking for 500 cars and an observation deck with a panoramic view of the center of the capital.
        \nThe stores of the shopping center present world-famous clothing brands, there is also
        a play area and a food court. There is a park area in front of the Neksta building: visitors
        can stroll along a shady alley and enjoy the mesmerizing view of the light and music fountain.</string>
    <string name="info_shopping_megaplanet">One of the largest shopping and leisure centers in Tashkent.
        In the Mega Planet mall you can not only shop, but also have a good rest. There is also a
        playground with professional educators, various cafes and restaurants, cinemas. MEGA PLANET
        is a modern shopping and entertainment complex that represents a new format of shopping and
        entertainment for a fun and comfortable leisure time for the whole family.</string>
    <string name="info_museums_nature">State Museum of Nature of Uzbekistan is located in Tashkent. It
        was established in July 12, 1876. The museum collection consists of 400 000 items, 300,000 of
        them are insects, 11000 - herbarium sheets, as well as many other zoological and geological materials.
        \nThe museum has four sections:\n- Department of Geology and Geography\n- Departments of flora
        and fauna\n- Scientific and Educational Department\n- Stock departmen.\nInvaluable collection
        funds were collected by expeditions for many years. Thus, the Museum of Nature of the Republic
        of Uzbekistan became the main museum of the country. The museum exposition has many exhibits
        of the origin of the first life on Earth, nature and the natural resources of the Republic.</string>
    <string name="info_museums_zoo">From the earliest days Tashkent Zoo has become a popular place
        for locals and guests of the capital. In one of the most picturesque parts of the city on an
        area of 22.7 hectares there is an exhibition of the interesting fauna of Uzbekistan and the
        world, characterized by great diversity.\nYou can get personally acquainted with the life
        of animals in conditions close to nature by visiting enclosures with predators and other
        mammals, parrots, exotic birds and waterfowl, primates. Some of the most ancient inhabitants
        of the Earth - snakes feel at ease in a specially designed terrarium. The wonderful world of
        the deep sea and freshwater submitted with more than 130 species of fish, swimming in the
        beautiful aquariums. For the youngest visitors here operates a petting zoo where children
        are in close proximity to animals watching their life can touch the turtle or guinea pigs,
        rabbits. Every year more and more adults and children come here to get closer to nature.</string>
    <string name="info_museums_victory">Victory Park was planned in honor of the 75th anniversary of
        the end of the Second World War. It was declared by President Shavkat Mirziyoyev in a holiday
        address on Victory Day in 2019. When describing the park, he said that it will be the \"practical
        embodiment of our admiration for the people\'s feat in that cruel war.\" It was also conceived
        during a visit by Russian President Vladimir Putin to Tashkent in October 2018. \nBuildings
        such as a \"Museum of Glory\" were be erected on the park\'s territory while designs such as
        an entrance arch were being installed. Historical memorabilia such as emblems, war flags and
        maps were added to the architectural ensemble of the park. The Ministry of Defense, the Ministry
        of Culture and the Academy of Sciences of Uzbekistan worked on the creation of the park as
        a joint project.</string>
    <string name="info_museums_temurids">Amir Timur Museum is a unique museum in Tashkent and can easily
        be declared as the best museum in town. The museum is one of a kind both because of the theme,
        which is anything related to the reign of Amir Timur, and the architectural structure of the
        building itself. There are two main floors and an hour would be enough to explore them both.
        \n The Museum inauguration was dated to 660 anniversary of Amir Timur. The Amir Timur Museum
        holds exhibits dedicated to the epoch of Timur and the Timurid dynasty. There, you can see
        beautiful miniatures reflecting events of that epoch. There is a copy of the Ottoman Koran
        in the central hall on the Museum ground floor. The walls of the hall, decorated by the best
        artists of Uzbekistan, show the scenes from Timur\’s life.</string>
    <string name="info_museums_railways">One of the most interesting sights in Tashkent is the Museum
        of Railway Engineering, or as the locals call it, the \"Museum of Steam Locomotives\". Children
        will especially like it, because museum exhibits can not only be touched by hands, but fully
        explored from the inside!\nThe museum itself is more like a park, it has an elongated shape
        of almost a kilometer, so excursions around it are carried out on a small train running through
        the territory. This is a favorite place for the residents of the capital of Uzbekistan,
        where they often shoot in retro style, wedding photo walks, and come with the whole family
        with children.</string>

    <string name="address_mosque_khazrati_imam">Karasaray str., 107/1, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_mosque_sheikh_zayniddin">Mannon Uyger str., 378, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_mosque_minor">Minor str., 1, Yunusobod district, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_mosque_islam_ota">Fargona yuli str., 51, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_mosque_shekh_muhammadsodik">Bektopi str., Chilanzar district, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_hyatt_regency">Navoi str., 1 A, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_hilton">Islam Karimov str. Block 5, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_ichan_qala">Tafakkur str., 24, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_wyndham"> Amir Temur Str., C-4, No. 7/8,Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_city_palace">Amir Temur str., 15, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_shopping_samarkand_darvoza">Karatash str., 5a, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_shopping_chorsu_bazaar">Tafakkur str., 57, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_shopping_yangiabad">Kuyi Talarik str., 1, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_shopping_next">Bobur str., 6, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_shopping_megaplanet">Akhmad Donish str., 2B, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_museums_nature">Zarkaynar str., 1, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_museums_zoo">Bogishamol str., 232A, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_museums_victory">Korakamish str., 2/1, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="address_museums_temurids">Amir Temur str., 13, Tashkent</string>

    <string name="address_museums_railways">Turkiston str., 6, Tashkent</string>
    <string name="phone_mosque_khazrati_imam"><u>tel:+998974904553</u></string>
    <string name="phone_mosque_sheikh_zayniddin"><u>tel:+998946922835</u></string>
    <string name="phone_mosque_minor"><u>tel:+998712351733</u></string>
    <string name="phone_mosque_islam_ota"><u>tel:+998712995882</u></string>
    <string name="phone_mosque_shekh_muhammadsodik"><u>tel:+998712175999</u></string>
    <string name="phone_hotel_hyatt_regency"><u>tel:+998712071234</u></string>
    <string name="phone_hotel_hilton"><u>tel:+998712108888</u></string>
    <string name="phone_hotel_ichan_qala"><u>tel:+998712319898</u></string>
    <string name="phone_hotel_wyndham"><u>tel:+998781203700</u></string>
    <string name="phone_hotel_city_palace"><u>tel:+998712383000</u></string>
    <string name="phone_shopping_samarkand_darvoza"><u>tel:+998712050055</u></string>
    <string name="phone_shopping_chorsu_bazaar"><u>tel:+998974904553</u></string>
    <string name="phone_shopping_yangiabad"><u>tel:+998712983929</u></string>
    <string name="phone_shopping_next"><u>tel:+998712312010</u></string>
    <string name="phone_shopping_megaplanet"><u>tel:+998781293131</u></string>
    <string name="phone_museums_nature"><u>tel:+998712070317</u></string>
    <string name="phone_museums_zoo"><u>tel:+99871289095</u></string>
    <string name="phone_museums_victory"><u>tel:+998974904553</u></string>
    <string name="phone_museums_temurids"><u>tel:+998712320766</u></string>
    <string name="phone_museums_railways"><u>tel:++998712997040</u></string>

    <string name="work_time_mosque_khazrati_imam">05:30 – 21:30</string>
    <string name="work_time_mosque_sheikh_zayniddin">05:30 – 21:30</string>
    <string name="work_time_mosque_minor">05:30 – 21:30</string>
    <string name="work_time_mosque_islam_ota">05:30 – 21:30</string>
    <string name="work_time_mosque_shekh_muhammadsodik">05:30 – 21:30</string>
    <string name="work_time_hotel_hyatt_regency">24/7</string>
    <string name="work_time_hotel_hilton">24/7</string>
    <string name="work_time_hotel_ichan_qala">24/7</string>
    <string name="work_time_hotel_wyndham">24/7</string>
    <string name="work_time_hotel_city_palace">24/7</string>
    <string name="work_time_shopping_samarkand_darvoza">10:00 – 22:30</string>
    <string name="work_time_shopping_chorsu_bazaar">05:00 – 20:15</string>
    <string name="work_time_shopping_yangiabad">07:00 – 19:00 only Saturday and Sunday</string>
    <string name="work_time_shopping_next">10:00 – 22:00</string>
    <string name="work_time_shopping_megaplanet">10:00 – 22:00</string>
    <string name="work_time_museums_nature">10:00 – 16:00</string>
    <string name="work_time_museums_zoo">09:00 – 18:00</string>
    <string name="work_time_museums_victory">09:00 – 19:00</string>
    <string name="work_time_museums_temurids">10:00 – 17:00</string>
    <string name="work_time_museums_railways">08:30 – 19:00</string>

    <string name="title_general_view">General view</string>
    <string name="title_rooms">Rooms</string>
    <string name="title_pool">Pool</string>
    <string name="title_dinning">Dinning</string>
    <string name="title_bath_room">Bath room</string>
    <string name="title_new_day">New Day</string>
    <string name="title_khonakoh">Khonakoh</string>
    <string name="title_wash_room">Wash room</string>
    <string name="title_welcoma">Welcome</string>
    <string name="title_mesmerizing_dome">Mesmerizing dome</string>
    <string name="title_good_night">Good night</string>
    <string name="title_dawn">Dawn</string>
    <string name="title_under_the_floor">Under the floor</string>
    <string name="title_toilets">Toilets</string>
    <string name="title_mosque_yard">Mosque Yard</string>
    <string name="title_nica_day">Nice Day</string>
    <string name="title_minaret">Minaret</string>
    <string name="title_white_black">White in Black</string>
    <string name="title_entrance_door">Entrance doors</string>
    <string name="title_steam_lokomotives">Steam locomotives</string>
    <string name="title_biggest_steam_lokomotives">Biggest Steam locomotive</string>
    <string name="title_biggest_armored_lokomotives">Armored locomotive</string>
    <string name="title_railway_station">Railway station\nfor traveling through</string>
    <string name="title_railway_traveling_throught">Railway station\nfor traveling \nthrough
        the museum</string>
    <string name="title_ottoman_quran">Ottoman Koran\nin the central hall</string>
    <string name="title_exhibit_timurid_era">Exhibits of the\nTimurid era</string>
    <string name="title_miniature_exhibits">Miniature exhibits</string>
    <string name="title_floors">Floors</string>
    <string name="title_show_room_jurrasic_peiod">Show room of\nJurrasic peiod</string>
    <string name="title_entomological_collection">Entomological collection</string>
    <string name="title_stuffed_real_animals">Stuffed Real Animals</string>
    <string name="title_stuffed_sheeps">Stuffed sheep in the desert</string>
    <string name="title_road_to_museum_of_honor">The road to the\nmuseum of honor</string>
    <string name="title_trenches_and_tanks">Real trenches and tanks</string>
    <string name="title_wax_figures">Wax figures</string>
    <string name="title_real_techniques">Only real techniques</string>
    <string name="title_old_railway_station">Railway station in 1941</string>
    <string name="title_zoo_entrance">Zoo entrance doors</string>
    <string name="title_black_bears">Black Bears</string>
    <string name="title_pride_of_lions">Pride of Lions</string>
    <string name="title_asian_elephant">Asian Elephant</string>
    <string name="title_welcoming_peacock">Welcoming Peacock</string>
    <string name="title_play_area">Play Area</string>
    <string name="title_brand_stores">Brand Stores</string>
    <string name="title_food_court">Food Court</string>
    <string name="title_musical_fountain">Musical Fountain</string>
    <string name="title_ice_rink">Ice Rink</string>
    <string name="title_ice_city">Ice City</string>
    <string name="title_makro_market">Makro Market</string>
    <string name="title_antique_furnitures">Antique furnitures</string>
    <string name="title_unique_jewelry">Unique jewelry</string>
    <string name="title_antiques">Antiques</string>
    <string name="title_old_musical_instruments">Old musical instruments</string>
    <string name="title_pet_shops">Pet shops</string>
    <string name="title_dome_market">Dome market</string>
    <string name="title_craftsmen">Сraftsmen</string>
    <string name="title_art_knifes">Art knives</string>
    <string name="title_dried_fruits">Dried fruits</string>

    <string name="tab_title_hyatt_regency">Hyatt\nRegency</string>
    <string name="tab_title_hilton">Hilton</string>
    <string name="tab_title_ichan_qala">Ichan\nQal\'a</string>
    <string name="tab_title_wyndham">Wyndham</string>
    <string name="tab_title_city_palace">City\nPalace</string>
    <string name="tab_title_khazrati_imam">Khazrati\nImam</string>
    <string name="tab_title_sheikh_zayniddin">Sheikh\nZayniddin</string>
    <string name="tab_title_minor">Minor</string>
    <string name="tab_title_islam_ota">Islam\nOta</string>
    <string name="tab_title_muhammad_sadyk">Sheikh Muhammad Sadyk\nMuhammad Yusuf</string>
    <string name="tab_title_museum_nature">State Museum of\nNature of Uzbekistan</string>
    <string name="tab_title_tashkent_zoo">Tashkent\nZoo</string>
    <string name="tab_title_victory_park">Victory\nPark</string>
    <string name="tab_title_amir_temur_museum">Amir Timur\nMuseum</string>
    <string name="tab_title_railway_museum">Railway\nMuseum</string>
    <string name="tab_title_samarkand_darvoza">Mall Samarkand\nDavroza</string>
    <string name="tab_title_chorsu_bazaar">Chorsu\nBazaar</string>
    <string name="tab_title_Yangiobod_market">Yangiobod Weekend\nFlea Marketa</string>
    <string name="tab_title_next">Mall\nNext</string>
    <string name="tab_title_megaplanet">Mega\nPlanet</string>
    <string name="mosques">Mosques</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="shopping">Shopping</string>
    <string name="museums_amp_zoo"><![CDATA[Museums & Zoo]]></string>

</resources>